Frances Wasserlein fonds
Simon Fraser University Archives and Records Management Department
Frances Wasserlein fonds
1895 - 1990
F-162
Q100144173
75 cm of textual records 34 photographs: slides 22 sound recordings
Simon Fraser University Archives and Records Management Department Maggie Benston Student Services Building, Rm. 0400 8888 University Dr. Burnaby British Columbia Canada V5A 1S6 Telephone: 778.782.3805 Email: archives@sfu.ca http://www.sfu.ca/archives
DATES OF CREATION The dates given (1895-1990) reflect the dates of the documents, including published research material Wasserlein collected in the course of writing her thesis. Her files were mainly accumulated over the period 1979-1990. PHYSICAL DESCRIPTION Physical description: 34 photographs (slides) are located in file F-162-3-3-0-28. TERMS OF USE AND REPRODUCTION Copyright subsists in all or some of the records and the donor, Frances Wasserlein, has retained copyright ownership. Generally, the donor only owns copyright to the works s/he authored and not necessarily to all the records that comprise this fonds or collection. The Archives can make a single copy only for private study, research, or other fair dealing use by a patron. The donor has granted the Archives permission to release her contact information to those researchers wishing to ask permission to copy and use the copyright protected materials for a different purpose. Speak with the Reference Archivist for details.
Wasserlein, Frances
Frances Wasserlein is a feminist, historian and social activist. Her research and social activism has focused on issues surrounding women's liberation. She completed a Master of Arts degree in history at Simon Fraser University in 1990. Her thesis, "An Arrow Aimed at the Heart": the Vancouver Women's Caucus and the Abortion Campaign, 1969-1971, investigated the history of the Vancouver Women's Caucus (VWC) and their organizing work for the Abortion Caravan from Vancouver to Ottawa in 1970.
Wasserlein was raised in Vancouver. She graduated from the University Program at Little Flower Academy in 1964. Wasserlein acknowledges becoming a feminist in 1976. At the time she was working as a secretary at the University of British Columbia (UBC). Her involvement with the union, and a summer job working at Vancouver Rape Relief contributed to an interest in social justice and social change. In April 1977 she left her job at UBC and began full time undergraduate studies at that university. She completed a BA (honors) in history in 1980.
During the summer of 1979 Wasserlein worked as a researcher for the Women's Office at UBC on a project related to the early contributions of women to the establishment of UBC and the role women played in student activism at the university. In 1979 and 1980 she worked with a small group of women to begin Battered Women's Support Services, providing self-help groups for women who were seeking an end to the violence that had driven them and their children from their homes.
After receiving her BA from UBC, Wasserlein worked for the YMCA as a co-manager of Munro House for eighteen months. Following that, she worked as a researcher and writer with the Women's Research Centre, working on studies related to the institutionalization of women's services. She supplemented her income by doing bookkeeping for various arts and non-profit organizations. Wasserlein worked on founding Women Against Violence Against Women (WAVAW) in 1982. She was also involved in the work of Women Against the Budget in 1983, a political group opposed to the legislation tabled by the Social Credit government following their victory in the 1983 provincial election.
Her interest in the source of conflict between and among individual women activists, and between and among women's organizations, motivated her to seek out the source of these conflicts by examining the history of women's movements in Canada. In 1982, she applied for a Canada Council grant for a women's history project she wished to undertake. The grant application was turned down. In 1985 she enrolled in a Master of Arts degree program in history at Simon Fraser University. After completing her MA, Wasserlein taught women's studies at Langara College in Vancouver, BC until 1997. She has also worked as a sessional instructor at SFU. As of 2002, she was employed as the executive producer of the Vancouver Folk Music Festival.
published
Full
Revised
Title of the fonds is based on the name of the creator.
The fonds consists primarily of records created during the writing of Wasserlein's MA thesis at SFU, "An Arrow Aimed at the Heart": the Vancouver Women's Caucus and the Abortion Campaign, 1969-1971, completed in 1990. The fonds also contains records related to other research Wasserlein was involved in, specifically her work with the UBC research project on non-academic women in 1979, and her application for a Canada Council grant in support of her own research project in 1982. Fonds includes taped interviews, transcripts, notes, drafts, correspondence, published materials, periodicals, and photographs. No records exist related to Wasserlein's activities with the Vancouver Folk Music Festival.
Original order was maintained where possible. In cases where no order was apparent, the archivist imposed an arrangement.
Sound recordings; Photographic materials; Textual records; Women
Contents of the fonds were donated to the SFU Archives by Frances Wasserlein.
All accessions have been processed as of March 2006. No further accruals are expected.
The original accession contained material belonging to the fonds of Andrea Lebowitz, F-164; Candace Parker, F-165; and Anne Roberts, F-166. See the inventories for these fonds.
Some files may contain personal or confidential information. Access to cassette interviews and transcripts is restricted until 2045, as stipulated by Archives policy or the donor. Files marked 'pending review' must be reviewed by an archivist prior to release, and as a result of the review access restrictions may apply. Please see the file lists and consult the archivist for more details.
Series descriptions and file and item lists are available.
- UBC Project on Non Academic Women records, 1979; F-162-1; 1 cm of textual records
  published
  Series consists of notes, correspondence, memos, lists of names, questionnaires, and receipts related to Frances Wasserlein's involvement with a project to produce a history of the Dean of Women's Office at UBC, then known as the Women Students' Office.
  University of British Columbia (UBC)
  Series is open with no access restrictions.
  A file list is available.
  - Non-Academic Women: History of Women at UBC, 1979; F-162-1-0-0-1 (Archival box - standard 162-1)
    Textual records
    Open
  - Correspondence re Project - History of Women at UBC, 1979; F-162-1-0-0-2 (Archival box - standard 162-1)
- Canada Council Grant Application, 1982 - 1983; F-162-2; 1 cm of textual records
  Series consists of one file of notes, drafts, correspondence, receipts and copies of Frances Wasserlein's Canada Council Grant application in 1982. The grant application was made to request support for writing a book about the history of the women's liberation movement in British Columbia.
  Canada Council for the Arts
  - Canada Council, 1982 - 1983; F-162-2-0-0-1 (Archival box - standard 162-1)
- MA Thesis records, 1895 - 1990; F-162-3; 82 cm of textual records 34 photographs: slides 22 sound recordings; Physical description: 34 photographs (slides) are located in file F-162-3-3-0-28.
  Series consists of materials used by Frances Wasserlein in producing her MA thesis, written between 1985 and1990, "An Arrow Aimed at the Heart": the Vancouver Women's Caucus and the Abortion Campaign, 1969-1971. The thesis topic was the history of the Vancouver Women's Caucus (VWC) and the abortion campaign of 1969-1971. The series consists of taped interviews with VWC members; transcripts of the interviews; notes; drafts; bibliographies; correspondence; publications of women's liberation organizations in Canada and the United States; a scrapbook compiled by Wasserlein during her research; copies of the VWC newspaper, The Pedestal; photographs; and other miscellaneous papers and publications.
  The series has been arranged by the archivist into sub-series based on the types of materials.
  Vancouver Women's Caucus
  Access to materials relating to the interviews is restricted; see sub-series F-162-3-2 description for details and consult the reference archivist for more information about accessing these records.
  File and item lists are available.
  - Notes and Drafts, 1960 - 1990; F-162-3-1; 10 cm of textual records
    Sub-series consists of records related to the production of draft copies of Wasserlein's MA thesis. The sub-series contains notes, outlines, bibliographies, resource lists, a newspaper index, newspaper clippings, correspondence, chapter drafts and a draft final copy.
    The series is open with no access restrictions.
    - MA Thesis - Various Notes, Lists, etc., 1985 - 1990; F-162-3-1-0-1 (Archival box - standard 162-1)
    - MA Thesis - Miscellaneous Notes, 1987 - 1990; F-162-3-1-0-2 (Archival box - standard 162-1)
    - MA Thesis - Notes - Vancouver Women's Caucus, 1988; F-162-3-1-0-3 (Archival box - standard 162-1)
    - Miscellaneous Notes and Documents, 1960 - 1990; F-162-3-1-0-4 (Archival box - standard 162-1)
    - MA Thesis - Timeline: Women's Liberation Movement, Vancouver, 1968 - 1972; F-162-3-1-0-5 (Archival box - standard 162-1)
    - MA Thesis - Newspaper Index - The Province, 1985; F-162-3-1-0-6 (Archival box - standard 162-1)
    - MA Thesis - Newspaper Index - Vancouver Sun, 1985; F-162-3-1-0-7 (Archival box - standard 162-1)
    - MA Thesis - Newspaper Index - Georgia Straight, 1985; F-162-3-1-0-8 (Archival box - standard 162-1)
    - MA Thesis - Newspaper Index - Misc. Newspapers, 1985; F-162-3-1-0-9 (Archival box - standard 162-1)
    - MA Thesis - BC News Index, 1985; F-162-3-1-0-10 (Archival box - standard 162-1)
    - MA Thesis - Bibliography and Notes, 1985; F-162-3-1-0-11 (Archival box - standard 162-1)
    - MA Thesis - Drafts 1/2, 1981 - 1990; F-162-3-1-0-12 (Archival box - standard 162-1)
    - MA Thesis - Drafts 2/2, 1981 - 1990; F-162-3-1-0-13 (Archival box - standard 162-1)
    - MA Thesis - Draft, Final Version, 1990; F-162-3-1-0-14 (Archival box - standard 162-1)
  - Interviews, 1986 - 1987; F-162-3-2; 13 cm of textual records 19 sound recordings; Physical description: sub-series includes 70 audio cassettes (originals and copies); as of October 2012, none of the recordings have been digitized. General note: there is no sound recording for one of the interviews (Hellen Potrebenko).
    Sub-series consists of records related to interviews conducted by Wasserlein with members of the Vancouver Women's Caucus. The sub-series contains tape recorded interviews, interview transcripts, correspondence with interview subjects, a notebook, and reference copies of the interview cassettes created by the archives.
    Files are arranged alphabetically by interviewee. The sound recordings of the interviews are linked via the reference code to the paper file containing transcripts and other textual records.
    Access to cassette interviews and transcripts is restricted to protect the privacy of the interviewees as stipulated in the donation agreement between the donor and the Archives. Restrictions expire January 1, 2045. Prior to this date, the Archives will provide access only under the terms and conditions of a Research Agreement; consult the reference archivist for more information.
    For preservation reasons, access to the sound recordings is restricted due to the age and fragility of the cassettes. The Archives will provide access only through digitization of the originals. As of October 2012, no interviews have been digitized. Consult the reference archivist for more information about accessing the sound recordings.
    - Thesis Correspondence, 1986 - 1987; F-162-3-2-0-1 (Archival box - standard 162-2)
    - Women's Caucus Reunion Notebook, 1986; F-162-3-2-0-2 (Archival box - standard 162-2)
      Restricted in whole
    - MA Thesis Interview - Benston, Margaret, 1986; F-162-3-2-0-3 (Archival box - standard 162-2)
      Benston, Maggie; Textual records
      - MA Thesis Interview Tape - Benston, Margaret, 6 October 1986; F-162-3-2-0-3-1 (Audio cassette OBJ-3567, Audio cassette OBJ-3568, Audio cassette OBJ-3603, Audio cassette OBJ-3604)
        Sound recordings
        Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: C-162-3-2-0-1 (orig.), F-162-item1, F-162-item2, F-162-item42, F-162-item43.
    - MA Thesis Interview - Briemberg, Elizabeth, 1986; F-162-3-2-0-4 (Archival box - standard 162-2)
      Briemberg, Elizabeth; Textual records
      - MA Thesis Interview Tape - Briemberg, Elizabeth, 19 October 1986; F-162-3-2-0-4-1 (Audio cassette OBJ-3569, Audio cassette OBJ-3570, Audio cassette OBJ-3605, Audio cassette OBJ-3606)
        Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: C-162-3-2-0-3 (orig.), F-162-item3, F-162-item4, F-162-item44, F-162-item45.
    - MA Thesis Interview - Cohen, Marcy, 1986; F-162-3-2-0-5 (Archival box - standard 162-2)
      Marcy Cohen; Textual records
      - MA Thesis Interview Tape - Cohen, Marcy, 30 September 1986; F-162-3-2-0-5-1 (Audio cassette OBJ-3571, Audio cassette OBJ-3572, Audio cassette OBJ-3607, Audio cassette OBJ-3608)
        Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: C-162-3-2-0-5 (orig.), F-162-item5, F-162-item6, F-162-item46, F-162-item47.
    - MA Thesis Interview - Davitt (Hoffer), Patricia, 1986; F-162-3-2-0-6 (Archival box - standard 162-2)
      Patricia Davitt; Textual records
      - MA Thesis Interview Tape - Davitt (Hoffer), Patricia, 9 October 1986; F-162-3-2-0-6-1 (Audio cassette OBJ-3573, Audio cassette OBJ-3574, Audio cassette OBJ-3609, Audio cassette OBJ-3610)
        Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: C-162-3-2-0-7 (orig.), F-162-item7, F-162-item8, F-162-item48, F-162-item49.
    - MA Thesis Interview - Dunn, Margo, 1986; F-162-3-2-0-7 (Archival box - standard 162-2)
      Dunn, Margo; Textual records
      - MA Thesis Interview Tape - Dunn, Margo, 8 October 1986; F-162-3-2-0-7-1 (Audio cassette OBJ-3575, Audio cassette OBJ-3576, Audio cassette OBJ-3577, Audio cassette OBJ-3611, Audio cassette OBJ-3612, Audio cassette OBJ-3613)
        Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: C-162-3-2-0-9 (orig.), F-162-item9, F-162-item10, F-162-item11, F-162-item50, F-162-item51, F-162-item52.
    - MA Thesis Interview - Flood, Cynthia, 1986; F-162-3-2-0-8 (Archival box - standard 162-2)
      Flood, Cynthia; Textual records
      - MA Thesis Interview Tape - Flood, Cynthia, 9 October 1986; F-162-3-2-0-8-1 (Audio cassette OBJ-3578, Audio cassette OBJ-3614)
        Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: C-162-3-2-0-12 (orig.), F-162-item12, F-162-item53.
    - MA Thesis Interview - Hager, Sharon, 1986; F-162-3-2-0-9 (Archival box - standard 162-2)
      Sharon Hager; Textual records
      - MA Thesis Interview Tape - Hager, Sharon, 1 October 1986; F-162-3-2-0-9-1 (Audio cassette OBJ-3579, Audio cassette OBJ-3615)
        Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: C-162-3-2-0-13 (orig.), F-162-item13, F-162-item54.
    - MA Thesis Interview - Hollibaugh, Marge, 1986; F-162-3-2-0-10 (Archival box - standard 162-2)
      Hollibaugh, Marge; Textual records
      - MA Thesis Interview Tape - Hollibaugh, Marge 1/2, 7 October 1986; F-162-3-2-0-10-1 (Audio cassette OBJ-3580, Audio cassette OBJ-3581, Audio cassette OBJ-3616, Audio cassette OBJ-3617)
        Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: C-162-3-2-0-14 (orig.), F-162-item14, F-162-item15, F-162-item55, F-162-item56.
    - MA Thesis Interview - Liberson, Donna, 1986; F-162-3-2-0-11 (Archival box - standard 162-2)
      Donna Liberson; Textual records
      - MA Thesis Interview Tape - Liberson, Donna, 18 October 1986; F-162-3-2-0-11-1 (Audio cassette OBJ-3582, Audio cassette OBJ-3618, Audio cassette OBJ-3619)
        Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: C-162-3-2-0-16 (orig.), F-162-item16, F-162-item17, F-162-item57, F-162-item58.
    - MA Thesis Interview - Lebowitz, Andrea, 1986; F-162-3-2-0-12 (Archival box - standard 162-2)
      Lebowitz, Andrea; Textual records
      - MA Thesis Interview Tape - Lebowitz, Andrea, 18 October 1986; F-162-3-2-0-12-1 (Audio cassette OBJ-3583, Audio cassette OBJ-3584, Audio cassette OBJ-3620, Audio cassette OBJ-3621)
        Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: C-162-3-2-0-18 (orig.), F-162-item18, F-162-item19, F-162-item59, F-162-item60.
    - MA Thesis Interview - O'Donnell, Dorothy Jean, 1986; F-162-3-2-0-13 (Archival box - standard 162-2)
      Dorothy Jean O'Donnell; Textual records
      - MA Thesis Interview Tape - O'Donnell, Dorothy Jean, 4 November 1986; F-162-3-2-0-13-1 (Audio cassette OBJ-3585, Audio cassette OBJ-3586, Audio cassette OBJ-3587, Audio cassette OBJ-3622, Audio cassette OBJ-3623, Audio cassette OBJ-3624)
        Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: C-162-3-2-0-20 (orig.), F-162-item20, F-162-item21, F-162-item22, F-162-item61, F-162-item62, F-162-item63.
    - MA Thesis Interview - Parker, Candace, 1986; F-162-3-2-0-14 (Archival box - standard 162-2)
      Parker, Candace; Textual records
      - MA Thesis Interview Tape - Parker, Candace, 19 October 1986; F-162-3-2-0-14-1 (Audio cassette OBJ-3588, Audio cassette OBJ-3625)
        Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: C-162-3-2-0-23 (orig.), F-162-item23, F-162-item64.
    - MA Thesis Interview - Phillips, Esther, 1986; F-162-3-2-0-15 (Archival box - standard 162-2)
      Esther Phillips; Textual records
      - MA Thesis Interview Tape - Phillips, Esther, 20 October 1986; F-162-3-2-0-15-1 (Audio cassette OBJ-3589, Audio cassette OBJ-3590, Audio cassette OBJ-3626, Audio cassette OBJ-3627)
        Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: C-162-3-2-0-24 (orig.), F-162-item24, F-162-item25, F-162-item65, F-162-item66.
    - MA Thesis Interview - Potrebenko, Hellen, 1986; F-162-3-2-0-16 (Archival box - standard 162-2)
      Potrebenko, Helen; Textual records
    - MA Thesis Interview - Rands, Jean, 1986; F-162-3-2-0-17 (Archival box - standard 162-2)
      Jean Rands; Textual records
      - MA Thesis Interview Tape - Rands, Jean, 4 October 1986; F-162-3-2-0-17-1 (Audio cassette OBJ-3591, Audio cassette OBJ-3628, Audio cassette OBJ-3629)
        Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: C-162-3-2-0-26 (orig.), F-162-item26, F-162-item27, F-162-item67, F-162-item68.
    - MA Thesis Interview - Roberts, Anne, 1986; F-162-3-2-0-18 (Archival box - standard 162-2)
      Roberts, Anne; Textual records
      - MA Thesis Interview Tape - Roberts, Anne, 4 October 1986; F-162-3-2-0-18-1 (Audio cassette OBJ-3592, Audio cassette OBJ-3593, Audio cassette OBJ-3630, Audio cassette OBJ-3631)
        Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: C-162-3-2-0-28 (orig.), F-162-item28, F-162-item29, F-162-item69, F-162-item70.
    - MA Thesis Interview - Toms, Marcy, 1986; F-162-3-2-0-19 (Archival box - standard 162-2)
      Marcy Toms; Textual records
      - MA Thesis Interview Tape - Toms, Marcy, 11 October 1986; F-162-3-2-0-19-1 (Audio cassette OBJ-3594, Audio cassette OBJ-3595, Audio cassette OBJ-3632, Audio cassette OBJ-3633)
        Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: C-162-3-2-0-30 (orig.), F-162-item30, F-162-item31, F-162-item71, F-162-item72.
    - MA Thesis Interview - Walker, Cathy, 1986; F-162-3-2-0-20 (Archival box - standard 162-2)
      Walker, Cathy; Textual records
      - MA Thesis Interview Tape - Walker, Cathy, 30 September 1986; F-162-3-2-0-20-1 (Audio cassette OBJ-3596, Audio cassette OBJ-3634)
        Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: C-162-3-2-0-32 (orig.), F-162-item32, F-162-item73.
    - MA Thesis Interview - Wood (Meadley), Betsy, 1986; F-162-3-2-0-21 (Archival box - standard 162-2)
      Wood, Betsy; Textual records
      - MA Thesis Interview Tape - Wood (Meadley), Betsy, 21 October 1986; F-162-3-2-0-21-1 (Audio cassette OBJ-3597, Audio cassette OBJ-3598, Audio cassette OBJ-3635, Audio cassette OBJ-3636)
        Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: C-162-3-2-0-33 (orig.), F-162-item33, F-162-item34, F-162-item74, F-162-item75.
    - MA Thesis Interview - Woodsworth, Ellen, 1986; F-162-3-2-0-22 (Archival box - standard 162-2)
      Ellen Woodsworth; Textual records
      - MA Thesis Interview Tape - Woodsworth, Ellen, 4 October 1986; F-162-3-2-0-22-1 (Audio cassette OBJ-3599, Audio cassette OBJ-3600, Audio cassette OBJ-3637, Audio cassette OBJ-3638)
        Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: C-162-3-2-0-35 (orig.), F-162-item35, F-162-item36, F-162-item76, F-162-item77.
  - General Research Materials, 1895 - 1990; F-162-3-3; 46 cm of textual records 85 periodicals 34 photographs: slides; General note: 34 photographs (slides) are located in file F-162-3-3-0-28; digital copies are available (stored on 2 CDs).
    Sub-series consists of source material compiled by Wasserlein during the writing of her MA thesis. The sub-series contains a photocopy of a scrapbook produced by Marge Hollibaugh; notes; bibliographies; correspondence; publications from women's liberation organizations; proceedings from the Vancouver Indochinese Women's Conference, 1972; photographs from the Abortion Caravan to Ottawa, 1970; copies of the Vancouver Women's Caucus newspaper, The Pedestal; and photocopies of other miscellaneous published material.
    - Vancouver Women's Caucus Binder, 1969; F-162-3-3-0-1 (Archival box - standard 162-3)
    - Vancouver Women's Caucus Binder 1/3, 1969; F-162-3-3-0-2 (Archival box - standard 162-3)
    - Vancouver Women's Caucus Binder 2/3, 1969; F-162-3-3-0-3 (Archival box - standard 162-3)
    - Vancouver Women's Caucus Binder 3/3, 1969; F-162-3-3-0-4 (Archival box - standard 162-3)
    - Vancouver Women's Caucus Binder 1/5, 1970; F-162-3-3-0-5 (Archival box - standard 162-3)
    - Vancouver Women's Caucus Binder 2/5, 1970; F-162-3-3-0-6 (Archival box - standard 162-3)
    - Vancouver Women's Caucus Binder 3/5, 1970; F-162-3-3-0-7 (Archival box - standard 162-3)
    - Vancouver Women's Caucus Binder 4/5, 1970; F-162-3-3-0-8 (Archival box - standard 162-4)
    - Vancouver Women's Caucus Binder 5/5, 1970; F-162-3-3-0-9 (Archival box - standard 162-4)
    - Vancouver Women's Caucus Binder 1/3, 1970; F-162-3-3-0-10 (Archival box - standard 162-4)
    - Vancouver Women's Caucus Binder 2/3, 1970; F-162-3-3-0-11 (Archival box - standard 162-4)
    - Vancouver Women's Caucus Binder 3/3, 1970; F-162-3-3-0-12 (Archival box - standard 162-4)
    - International Women's Day, 1948 - 1967; F-162-3-3-0-13 (Archival box - standard 162-4)
    - Women's Liberation Movement - Chatelaine - Abortion, 1959 - 1971; F-162-3-3-0-14 (Archival box - standard 162-4)
    - Women's Liberation Movement - Bibliographies and Lists, 1986; F-162-3-3-0-15 (Archival box - standard 162-4)
    - Women's Liberation Movement - Notes on Documents, 1985 - 1990; F-162-3-3-0-16 (Archival box - standard 162-4)
    - Women's Liberation Movement - Abortion Articles, 1970 - 1971; F-162-3-3-0-17 (Archival box - standard 162-4)
    - Women's Liberation Movement - Various photocopied Articles, 1895 - 1976; F-162-3-3-0-18 (Archival box - standard 162-4)
    - Women's Liberation Movement - Documents, 1969 - 1970; F-162-3-3-0-19 (Archival box - standard 162-4)
    - Women's Liberation Movement - photocopied Documents, 1985 - 1990; F-162-3-3-0-20 (Archival box - standard 162-4)
    - BC Women's Liberation Movement - History 1/2, 1975 - 1985; F-162-3-3-0-21 (Archival box - standard 162-5)
    - BC Women's Liberation Movement - History 2/2, 1973; F-162-3-3-0-22 (Archival box - standard 162-5)